buychina.com 2016-11-25

# Buy China Wholesale from Taobao Agent online shopping - BuyChina.com

We can make our services even better – to show you more relevant search results and products, to help you connect with people or to make sharing with others quicker and easier. As you use our services, we want you to be clear how we’re using information and the ways in which you can protect your privacy. 

Our Privacy Policy explains: 

  * What information we collect and why we collect it. 
  * How we use that information. 
  * The choices we offer, including how to access and update information. 

Your privacy matters to BuyChina so whether you are new to BuyChina or a long-time user, please do take the time to get to know our practices – and if you have any questions contact us. 

##  Information we collect 

We collect information to provide better services to all of our users – from figuring out basic stuff like which language you speak, to more complex things like which products you’ll find most useful or the people who matter most to you online. 

We collect information in two ways: 

  * Information you give us. When you sign up for a BuyChina Account, we’ll ask for personal information, like your name, email address, telephone number or credit card. 
  * Information we get from your use of our services. We may collect information about the services that you use and how you use them. This information includes: 

  * **Device information**

We may collect device-specific information (such as your hardware model, operating system version, unique device identifiers, and mobile network information including phone number). BuyChina may associate your device identifiers or phone number with your BuyChina Account. 

  * **Log information**

When you use our services or view content provided by BuyChina, we may automatically collect and store certain information in server logs. This may include: 

  * details of how you used our service, such as your visit history. 
  * telephony log information like your phone number, calling-party number, forwarding numbers, time and date of calls, duration of calls, SMS routing information and types of calls. 
  * Internet protocol address(IP Address). 
  * device event information such as crashes, system activity, hardware settings, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and referral URL. 
  * cookies that may uniquely identify your browser or your BuyChina Account. 

  * **Location information**

When you use a location-enabled BuyChina service, we may collect and process information about your actual location, like GPS signals sent by a mobile device. We may also use various technologies to determine location, such as sensor data from your device that may, for example, provide information on nearby Wi-Fi access points and cell towers. 

  * **Local storage**

We may collect and store information (including personal information) locally on your device using mechanisms such as browser web storage (including HTML 5) and application data caches. 

  * **Cookies and anonymous identifiers**

We use various technologies to collect and store information when you visit BuyChina.com, and this may include sending one or more cookies or anonymous identifiers to your device. 

##  How we use information we collect 

We use the information we collect from all of our services to provide, maintain, protect and improve them, to develop new ones, and to protect BuyChina and our users. We also use this information to offer you tailored content – like giving you more relevant search results and products. 

We may use the name you provide for your BuyChina Profile across all of the services we offer that require a BuyChina Account. In addition, we may replace past names associated with your BuyChina Account so that you are represented consistently across all our services. If other users already have your email, or other information that identifies you, we may show them your publicly visible BuyChina Profile information, such as your name and photo. 

When you contact BuyChina, we may keep a record of your communication to help solve any issues you might be facing. We may use your email address to inform you about our services, such as letting you know about upcoming changes or improvements. 

We use information collected from cookies and other technologies to improve your user experience and the overall quality of our services. For example, by saving your language preferences, we’ll be able to have our services appear in the language you prefer. When showing you related products, we will not associate a cookie or anonymous identifier with sensitive categories, such as those based on race, religion, sexual orientation or health. 

We may combine personal information from one service with information, including personal information, from other BuyChina services – for example to make it easier to share things with people you know. 

We will ask for your consent before using information for a purpose other than those that are set out in this Privacy Policy. 

BuyChina processes personal information on our servers in many countries around the world. We may process your personal information on a server located outside the country where you live. 

##  Information you share 

Many of our services let you share information with others. Remember that when you share information publicly, it may be indexable by search engines, such as Google.com. Our services provide you with different options on sharing and removing your content. 

##  Accessing and updating your personal information 

Whenever you use our services, we aim to provide you with access to your personal information. If that information is wrong, we strive to give you ways to update it quickly or to delete it – unless we have to keep that information for legitimate business or legal purposes. When updating your personal information, we may ask you to verify your identity before we can act on your request. 

We may reject requests that are unreasonably repetitive, require disproportionate technical effort (for example, developing a new system or fundamentally changing an existing practice), risk the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes). 

Where we can provide information access and correction, we will do so for free, except where it would require a disproportionate effort. We aim to maintain our services in a manner that protects information from accidental or malicious destruction. Because of this, after you delete information from our services, we may not immediately delete residual copies from our active servers and may not remove information from our backup systems. 

##  Information we share 

We do not share personal information with companies, organizations and individuals outside of BuyChina unless one of the following circumstances apply: 

  * **With your consent**

We will share personal information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of BuyChina when we have your consent to do so. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information. 

  * **For external processing**

We provide personal information to our affiliates or other trusted businesses or persons to process it for us, based on our instructions and in compliance with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 

  * **For legal reasons**

We will share personal information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of BuyChina if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to: 

  * meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request. 
  * enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations. 
  * detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues. 
  * protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of BuyChina, our users or the public as required or permitted by law. 

##  Enforcement 

We regularly review our compliance with our Privacy Policy. We also adhere to several self regulatory frameworks. When we receive formal written complaints, we will contact the person who made the complaint to follow up. We work with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that we cannot resolve with our users directly. 

##  Changes 

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of privacy policy changes). We will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.
